剧情回顾
previously on lost
Jason
这些人很聪明
These people are smart
同时还很残忍  如果你认为
and there animals If you think
仅凭单枪匹马
that one gun and one bullet
就能阻止他们
is gonna stop them.
好好想想我的话吧
Think it again.
我要去找我的儿子
I am going to find my son
没人能阻止我  明白吗
and nobody is gonna to stop me, okay?
-我和你一起去  -不行  就我一个
-I'll go with you  -No, I have to do it alone.
我打算越过底线
I'm going out the line where I'm not suppose to cross
然后告诉他们我们已抓到你了
and telling them we got you.
他们决不会交出Walt的
They will not give you Walt.
Michael
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
Michael Michael
Michael
Jack  你去哪  或许他们放了他
Jack, where are you going? Maybe they just let him go.
放了他  他可就只有他一个
Let him go, he is alone.
他们只是仅仅把他推到丛林 Jack
They just put him out of the jungle.
就他一个
He is alone.
好吧
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's go.
过会见, Ana Lucia
See ya, Ana Lucia.
你看上去很疲惫啊
You look tired.
算吧  谢谢关心
Yeah, thanks.
怎么了
What?
你昨晚在哪里
Where were you last night?
在家呆着
Home.
整晚都在
All night?
对  给自己做了点晚饭  还看了会儿电视
Yeah. I cooked myself some dinner, watched some TV.
你看了什么节目
What'd you watch
让我们好好谈一下
Let's go for a drive.
还记得Jason Alder吗
Remember Jason Alder?
凌晨三点在停车场发现了他的尸体
Found him in a parking lot just after three in the morning.
他死后一小时才被人发现
He was dead an hour before anyone saw him.
在案发现场的垃圾桶里发现了一把枪
Crime Scene pulled a gun from the dumpster.
没有枪支登记记录
Registration was filed off.
没有指纹,也没有目击者
No prints. No witnesses.
他就像是被处死的
He was executed.
有凶手的线索吗
Any idea who did it?
是的  Ana  就是你干的
Yeah, Ana. You did.
这个人招供曾残忍地朝你开枪
This man confesses to shooting you in cold blood
但是你拒绝指证他  所以我们不得不放了他
and you refuse to ID him. So we had to cut him loose.
一周后  他就胸中五弹而亡
A week later, he shows up with five bullets in him
因为有人残忍地枪杀了他
because someone shot him in cold blood.
看来我应该请一个律师
Guess I should get a lawyer.
听着  我们都知道
Look, we both know
这会成为一个无头案
that this is gonna be a dead-end investigation.
但是  Ana  如果真是你干的...
But, Ana, if you did this...
真是你干的话  你应该让我来帮你
if you did this, you have to let me help you.
谢谢你  妈妈  但是我不需要你的帮助
Thanks, Mom, but I don't need your help.
你不要我的帮助 那你也应该从别人那里获得帮助
You don't want my help, you're gonna have to get it from somewhere else.
Ana  你是个警官
You're a police officer, Ana.
你不尊重我也就罢了  但是你至少得对得起这个职业
If you don't respect me, at least respect that.
那好  我不干了
Then I quit.
Henry
你打算怎样
what do you say?
Henry 你到底要绝食到什么时候
How long you gonna keep up this hunger strike, Henry?
我有没有告诉过你我曾是警察
I ever tell you I was a cop?
我这一生碰到过很多杀人犯
I've been around a lot of killers in my life.
你知道这些人中最让我惊奇的是什么吗
You know what surprises me the most about them?
那就是他们个个都很爱扯淡
How much they love to talk.
但是你和他们不同... Henry
But you're different, Henry.
还保持沉默
Quiet.
你咕哝些什么
What was that?
如果你想说什么的话,
If you're gonna say something
你就得说出声来
you're gonna have to speak...
你杀了我们中的两人
You killed two of us.
他们都是好人 都想放过你
Good people who were leaving you alone.
你才是杀人犯  Ana Lucia
You're the killer, Ana Lucia.
看上去他终于决定开口了
I guess he decided to start talking?
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Siounex Zhao校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Mike 来份龙舌兰酒加奎宁水
Mike. Tequila-tonic.
忙活了一整天吧
Long day
很高兴又见到你了
Good to see you again.
你在安检处检查过我
You "wanded" me at security.
请再来一杯
Another one, please.
你是怎么开始从事安检工作的
So how does one get into "wanding"?
不当警察后
One stops being a cop.
太巧了  我刚刚辞去医生的工作
What a coincidence. I just stopped being a doctor.
你为什么辞了
Why'd you quit?
不是我主动要辞
I didn't.
是我的儿子出卖了我 他告密说我在工作期间喝酒
My son ratted me out for drinking on the job.
谢谢你的酒
Thank you.
执照被吊销了
Lost my license.
是的  我知道  这听起来很搞笑
Yeah, I know, it's hilarious.
不  没有  我仅仅是想说
No, no, it's just that,
我不相信父母和他们的孩子
I don't believe that parents and their kids
可以一起工作
should work together.
因为矛盾实在太多了
Too many issues.
为你刚才的一番话干杯
I'll drink to that.
你去哪
So, where you headed?
悉尼  澳大利亚
Sydney. Sydney, Australia.
想一起去吗
You wanna come?
我是当真的
I'm serious.
我为什么要和你一起去悉尼
Why would I go to Sydney with you?
或许是命运将我们连在一块
Maybe fate to get us together
就像我们俩能够在这个机场一起喝酒一样
You know, like two drinks in an airport bar.
缘分为什么要这么做
Why would fate do that?
这是缘分一贯的行事方法
Same reason fate does anything
只有这样我们才可以互相帮助
so that we can help each other out.
你确实需要帮助  不是吗
You do need help, right?
除非你不需要
Unless you don't.
我在那儿干的事可能会比较危险
What I'm doing down there could be dangerous.
所以我需要有人能够来保护我  比如贴身保镖
I need someone to protect me, a bodyguard.
你就是绝佳的人选
It's perfect for someone
因为你刚从警察退下来
who "stopped being a cop".
我都不知道你的名字
I don't even know your name
我们还是都不要用真名吧
Ooh. Let's not use real names
不如这样  你给我取个名字
I'll tell you what, why don't you pick a name for me,
我也给你起个名字  如何
and then I'll pick one for you.
就叫你Tom吧
You look like a "Tom".
Tom  多棒的名字啊
Tom. What an excellent name.
那我就叫你...
And you should be a...
Sarah
为澳大利亚干杯
Australia.
发生什么了
What happened?
刮脸的时候刮伤了自己
I cut myself shaving.
舱里的那个人想要杀我
The guy in the hatch tried to kill me.
你没事吧
You OK?
我没事...
I'm fine.
但是他不会好过
But he won't be.
Ana?
怎么
What?
不要干傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
如果你是来道歉的话,
If you've come to apologize
那我原谅你用拐杖来打我
I forgive you for hitting me with your crutch.
我很庆幸我的头没被打破
I'm so glad my head didn't break it.
为什么
Why?
那可是个大问题
Now that's a broad question.
你为什么要去对付Ana Lucia而不是我
Why did you try to hurt Ana Lucia but not me?
我不知道你指什么  John
I'm not sure I know what you're getting at, John.
我被那扇爆炸飞出的门给压住了...陷于绝望中
I was trapped under that blast door....Helpless.
你本可以碾碎我的头颅
You could've crushed my skull.
但是你没有那样做
But you didn't do a thing.
你为什么没有动手
Why didn't you?
因为你也是个好人  John
Because you're one of the good ones, John.
什么   好在哪里
What? Good what?
好在哪已经无所谓了 无论怎样  我都会死
None of this matters. I'm dead anyway.
医生去做交易了
The doctor's gone to make a trade,
我们大家都很清楚当他一无所获回来时
and we both know he'll come back empty-handed, and then...
我就失去了存活下去的价值
I've lost my value.
要么Jack回来杀了我
So either Jack comes back here and kills me
要么我的人发现我被囚禁在此  他们来杀了我
or my people find out where I'm being held and they do it.
为什么你自己人会想来杀你
Why would your own people want to kill you?
因为那个带头大哥
Because the man in charge...
他是个了不起的人物  John
He's a great man, John,
是个睿智的人
a brilliant man.
但他从不会宽恕别人
But he is not a forgiving man.
我把事办砸了  所以他一定会杀了我
He'll kill me because I failed, John.
任务失败了
I failed my mission.
什么任务
What mission?
当我中了那个女人的圈套被抓后
When that woman caught me in her trap,
我才来到了这里
I was on my way here, John.
我是为你而来
I was coming for you.
Locke
Locke  出来
Locke, get out here!
Locke
John!
我用了20分钟才把这些东西给弄下来
I've been knocking those things down for 20 minutes.
把你那该死的手从我的芒果上拿开
Get your hands off my damn mangoes.
看不出你还很在行摘水果啊
Didn't figure you for the fruit-picking type.
你想怎样
What do you want?
我要一把枪
I need a gun.
我看要不这样
here's an idea
不如去找你的好朋友Jack   他就有枪
Why not go to your buddy Jack? He's got himself a gun.
我差点忘了
That's right
他还和Kate一起在林子里闲逛呢
he's still traipsing around the jungle with Kate.
如果你觉得他抢了你女朋友 你感到不爽的话
If you've got a problem because he's making time with your girlfriend,
不要把气撒在我头上
don't take it out on me, man.
你还是给我把枪吧
How about you just give me a gun?
你给我滚
Here's another idea: Scram.
你听到没有  滚  现在就给我滚
You heard me. Now, git!
Sarah
Sarah,快开门
Sarah, open the damn door!
很好  你还没有睡
Good, you're up.
是时候履行你的保镖职责了
It's time. Protection duty.
来吧  我们出发了
Come on, let's go.
喝了四天酒  无所事事
After four days of drinking and doing nothing,
现在是午夜时分  你到准备好出发了
now, in the middle of the night, you're ready to go?
对的  完全正确
That's exactly right.
是时候了  走吧
It's time, come on
命运在召唤我们  Sarah
Fate's calling, Sarah.
就在这了  靠边停车
This is it. Pull over, right here.
这就是你所需要的保护  因为在郊区
This is what you needed protection for? The suburbs?
就呆在车里
Just stay in the car.
我是不是还应该开着停车计费器
Should I keep the meter running?
我能进来吗
Can I come in
听着  他是我女儿
Look, she's my daughter
我当然有权见她
and I have every right to see her!
不  你没有这个权力   出去
No, you don't have a right. Get out!
我现在就要进去
I'm coming in here!
你不能阻拦我   她可是我女儿啊
You can't stop me! She is my daughter
走开
Get out! Get out of my house!
我给这房子付的按揭
I pay the mortgage on this house!
我就是想看看我的女儿   你到底哪根筋搭错不让我看
I wanna see my daughter!  What the hell is wrong with you?
不许你再回来
Don't you ever come back here!
我正在和那个女士说话
I was just having a conversation with the lady.
你需要帮助
You need help!
老兄  挖得不错
Dude, nice hole
怎么说  Hurley
What is it, Hurley?
你还记得我们做的无线电吗
man, you remember that radio we made?
我想我可以用它来放些音乐
I was thinking maybe I could get it to play some music.
为Libby放
You know, for Libby
但是它就奏效过一次  而且也是一瞬间
it worked only once, and then just for a minute.
后来我还试过几次
I've tried several times since
但是只有噪音
and only gotten static.
是这样的  即是只有杂音也行
Here's the thing: Even that would be good.
因为到时候  Libby会觉得
Because Libby would be like
"有这份心就好了" 那样我就能给她留下好印象
"It's the thought that counts. "And I'll score major points.
尤其是当她看到我在很努力地调台
Especially when she sees me holding it over my head.
那你为什么要用只能制造杂音的无线电来调台呢
And why would you hold a static-generating radio over your head?
在巴格达没有  无话不说(电影)  吗
They didn't have Say Anything in Baghdad?
非常好看
It's awesome.
电影里  那个主角拿着手提收音机
This dude gets his boom box,
在女主角家窗前
holds it over his head outside this chick's window,
给她放了些Peter gabriel的歌
and plays some Peter Gabriel song for her
然后那女孩就喜欢上他了
and, bam, the girl's his.
在她爸爸进监狱后  然后他就抱得美人归了
I mean, after her dad goes to jail. But then he gets her.
-我想我明白你的意思了  -你真该好好看看这部电影
-I think I get the idea.  -You should check it out sometime.
我是说如果我们能够离开这个小岛
I mean, if we ever, you know, get off this island.
如果你真想为Libby做些什么的话
If you want to do something nice for Libby
三公里外有一片美丽的沙滩
there's a beautiful beach three kilometers from here.
你可以带她去那边
You could take her there.
你觉得她会喜欢吗
You think she'd like that?
我带Shannon去过一次
I took Shannon there once.
Michael
能见效吗
So it worked?
你在说什么  John
What are you talking about, John?
你的那笔交易
Your deal. The trade.
如果他们交出Michael
If they gave us Michael...
他们什么也没给
They didn't give us anything.
这么说来他遇上你们是个巧合
So it was just a coincidence that he came wandering out?
当时我正大声喊叫  他一定是听到声音
I was shouting. He heard my voice.
怎么   难道你觉得他们放了Michael
What? They just let Michael go,
还希望我们继续履行交易
hoping we would keep up our end of the bargain?
你觉得他们来自慈善机构
You think they're on the honor system?
出来  出来  不管你是谁
Come out, come out, whoever you are.
我知道你在那儿
I know you're there.
别逼我出手
Don't make me come in after you.
是你啊
What do we got here?
小红帽来找大灰狼的枪
Was Little Red Riding Hood following the Big Bad Wolf back to his stash o' guns?
为何不现在就把枪给我呢
Why don't you gimme that one right there?
我什么都不会给你.
I ain't gonna "gimme" you nothing.
我们以前也谈过这个事情  Lucy
We've been through this, Lucy.
现在要干什么呢  小姑娘
What you gonna do now, muchacha?
来点音乐
We need some damn music in here.
她是谁
Who was she?
你指谁
Who was who?
那个女人
That woman.
Sarah  这可说来话长啊
She is a very long story, Sarah.
我叫Ana Lucia
It's Ana Lucia.
但我还是Tom
Well, I'm still Tom.
你很可悲  对  你就是那样的
You're pathetic, that's what you are.
你说得对极了
You bet your sweet ass I am.
为什么到这来
Why are you here?
我来这儿是因为我不想给我儿子道歉
I'm here because I can't apologize to my son.
他试着帮我
He tried to help me
我用不辞而别来感谢他
so I thanked him by cutting him off.
我用痛恨来回报他
I thanked him by hating him.
孩子  你来这也是因为同样的原因
You came here for the same reason I did, kiddo.
你逃出来
You ran away.
我的天啊
My, my.
看看这次命运又带来什么了(鸡尾酒吧)
Look what fate has delivered up this time.
来吧
Come on.
一起去喝一杯  然后我们可以借醉做对可怜虫
Let's go have a drink or ten and be pathetic together.
怎么样
What do you say?
不
No.
不去
随你便吧
It's your call.
小心行人
I'm walking here!
等等
Wait!
不要去
Don't.
我们离开悉尼吧
Let's just get the hell out of Sydney.
一起走吧  一起回去
Let's just go. Let's go back.
我已不能再回头了
I can't ever go back.
再见了  孩子
See ya, kiddo
怎么了
What?
你不想要我的联系电话吗
Don't you want my phone number?
你要是敢告诉别人...
You tell anyone about this,
我就杀了你
and I'll kill you.
那也要一起滚下桌子吧
Guess that takes cuddling off the table.
你好
there
进展如何
Oh! How's it going?
并不像你想象的那样
This isn't what it looks like.
然后呢... 那应该是怎样的
And what does it look like?
那个... 看上去像这样...
It looks like something...
其实不是
that it's not.
好吧
man
被你活捉了
I'm so busted.
Hurley  我在这不是想告诫你
Hurley, I'm not here to tell you
不要偷吃东西的
how to act around food.
不  我不是说这个
No, I'm not busted for that.
我是说被你逮住的...
I'm busted for...
是一些其他的事情
something else.
我找吃的,
I was packing the picnic
是因为我想带你去野餐
because I was kind of hoping that you'd wanna go with me.
就我们俩
You know, as an "us" thing.
本打算给你个惊喜
But it was a surprise.
真的吗
Really?
你真好
That's very sweet.
那你想去吗
So, do you wanna go?
去哪里
Where to?
去哪先保密  因为那还是个惊喜
Can that part still be a surprise?
你回来了
You're back.
那其他人呢  他们没有出现
So, the Others, they didn't show up?
没有
No.
但Michael回来了
Michael's back, though.
额头怎么了
What happened here?
那是我的错
My fault.
我忘记关浴室的水龙头,
I left the tap on in the bathroom sink,
结果Ana滑倒了  还撞伤了头
and Ana wiped out and hit her head on the counter.
再次抱歉
And I'm sorry, again.
没关系的  放心吧
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Jack
我想他醒过来了
I think he's waking up.
Michael
Michael?
Jack
你好
man.
我...这是在哪...
where...
我怎么会这样...
How did I get...
放松点  好吗  你又回到舱里了
Wait, try to take it easy, OK? You're back in the hatch.
-昨晚我们在丛林里发现了你  -我的头啊
-We found you out in the jungle last night.  -my head.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
John.
我找到他们了
I found them.
我离开后,
After I left
向北前进,
I hiked north.
回到了原来的地方
Back to where we were.
到了海滩,沿着海岸线走
Hiked to the beach, followed the shoreline.
一天后  我看见了一个人
A day later, I saw one.
他长什么样
What did he look like?
很脏
He was dirty.
破烂的衣服  没穿鞋
Worn clothing. No shoes.
看上去很普通  就像其他同伙一样
Simple.Just like the rest of them.
-像其他同伙一样  -对的
-Like the rest of them?  -Yeah.
他的人  其他同伙
His people. The Others.
我跟踪他回到营地
I followed him back to his camp.
他们  他们住在帐篷里  帆布帐篷
They live in tents. Canvas tents
是那种圆锥形帐篷
and teepees.
他们吃鱼干  比我们过得还差
They eat dried fish. They're worse off than we are.
他们有多少人
How many of them were there?
我数了下,有22个
I counted 22.
-那么船呢...  -我没有看到
-And the boat...  -I didn't see it.
你...你有没有看到Walt
Did you... Did you see Walt?
没有
No.
但我知道他肯定在那儿
But I know he's there.
那么他们带走的其他人怎么样了
What about everyone else they took?
辛迪   看到其他孩子了吗
Cindy? Did you see any other kids?
没有,没有看到孩子
No. No, no kids.
但我认为他们和我儿子在一起
But I think they're in the same place as my boy.
他们也有个舱房
They have a hatch.
你怎么会知道的
How do you know that they...
通往地下有不少金属门
There's a set of metal doors leading underground.
-还能是什么呢  -你认为那里就是孩子们被关的地方
-What else could it be?  -You think that's where they're keeping the kids?
他们日夜守候在那
They keep it guarded 24l7.
两个护卫  两把枪
Two guards, two guns.
那两把枪是我所看到的所有的武器 其他人都没有武器
And two guns is all I saw. They're barely armed.
大部分是老人  其中还有一半是女人
Most of them are old. And half of them are women.
我想...
I wanted to...
但我救不了他
I couldn't save him.
所以我回来告诉你们...
So I came back to tell you.
告诉你们我们有能力救他们
To tell you that we can take them.
只要我一恢复体力
As soon as I get my strength back
就带你们去那
I will take us back there.
我们要把我儿子救回来
And we are gonna get my boy back.
你是对的
You were right.
什么对的
Right about what?
关于Henry
About Henry.
你和Sayid当初如何对待他
What you and Sayid did to him when you first found him
你...你做得对
you were right.
我虽然不欣赏你的处理方式,
I don't like how you did it
但我不该阻止你们
but I shouldn't have gotten in your way.
当然你做了你觉得是对的事情
you did what you thought was right
尽管你是当时这么觉得  Jack.
at the time you thought it, Jack.
我只希望下次你在决定做什么事之前,
I just hope the next time you decide to do something
请先让我知道
you include me.
直觉告诉我  你现在就有话要和我说
And something tells me that's gonna be soon.
你听到Michael说的话了
You heard Michael.
我们能救他们
We can take them.
我们那位大胡子朋友告诫我们不要越过底线
Our friend with the beard told us not to cross the line.
John  这些人都是骗子
These people are liars, John.
该死的  我们为什么要这么迷信他们
Why the hell should we take their word on anything?
我完全同意
I couldn't agree more.
那么...
So,
现在怎么办
now what?
你们去哪
Where are you going?
从Sawyer那要回枪
To get our guns back from Sawyer.
我们需要你去说服他
We're gonna need you to help convince him.
谁来照顾Michael
Who's gonna take care of Michael?
我留下吧
I'll stay.
-你们去吧  -确定没问题吗
-You guys go ahead.  -You sure?
替我向Sawyer问好
Give Sawyer my best.
好的  我们很快就回来
All right. We'll be back soon.
小心头  就快到了
Watch your head. Almost there.
看过"the flintstones"吗
You ever watch The Flintstones?
当然
Sure
我在医院的时候一直看
I used to watch it all the time when I was in the hospital.
因为把屁股弄伤了
When I broke my hip.
那你有没有注意过Fred是如何判断
Did you ever notice how Fred would run
一遍又一遍地重复走过同一个地方
by the same thing over and over again?
这已经是第三次路过这棵树了
Third time past this tree.
那不是同一颗树
That's a different tree.
Hurley  如果你迷路的话没有关系的
Hurley, it's OK if you're lost.
老兄  我没有迷路  你要相信我
Dude, I'm not lost. Will you trust me?
我们马上就要漫步于
We're right about to walk
这个岛上最最神秘的沙滩上了
onto the most excellent secret beach on the island
看  够惊喜吧
and... surprise!
Hurley
这是我们的沙滩
this is our beach.
Jin在那里
There's Jin.
你想过没有 为什么不在这儿野餐呢
I tell you what, why not have the picnic here?
来吧,把毯子给我
Come on, give me the blankets.
毯子
Blankets?
你没有带毯子
You don't have any blankets?
饮料带了吗
How about drinks?
好吧  这样吧  我去搞定毯子
OK, I tell you what, I will handle the blankets
你去找Rose还有Bernard
you just track down Rose and Bernard.
我看到他们拿了酒
I saw them pull wine from the pallet.
好吗
OK?
酒
Oh. Wine.
很棒
Groovy.
也许喝多后
maybe if I get drunk enough
我会记起你从哪来
I'll remember where I know you from.
或许吧
Yeah.
好的
OK.
Sawyer
把书放下
Put the book down.
这可不是书  这是手稿
It's not a book, it's a manuscript.
我将是第一个 也是唯一一个
I'm about to be the first and only guy
幸运儿知道作者的人
to find out "whodunit".
我明白了  你们都很有空
I think I got it figured out, so cool your damn jets
在椰树旁闲逛
and walk around the coconut trees.
还剩10页没看完了
I got ten pages left.
想知道吗
Want to figure it out?
你发什么神经啊
What the hell is your problem, Doc?
是时候把枪还给我们了
It's time to give us the guns back.
你烧了书的结局
You burn the ending of my book...
-东西在哪  James  -你说呢
-Where are they, James?  -You too, Brutus?
带我们去吧  Sawyer  好吗
Just take us there. All right?
-别再耍花样了  -你带她来可怜我
-Quit playing around.  What? -You bring her along for a sympathy vote?
我对她已经没有感觉了  医生
She ain't in my head, Doc
你们俩何不到林子里玩去
so why don't you two just go play in the jungle?
带我们去拿枪  现在就去
Take us to the guns. Now.
那个贱人
Oh, that bitch.
她偷了我的枪
She stole my damn gun.
Ana Lucia.
她要枪干什么
Why would she need a gun?
这个小贱人
Son of a bitch!
Jack...
我有话和你说
I need to tell you something.
捡起来
Pick it up.
自己松绑
Cut yourself loose.
什么
What?
照我说的做
Just do it.
为什么
Why?
你知道为什么
You know why.
他老说你误解了
He kept saying you were misunderstood.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
Goodwin.
是的  他说了你的一切  Ana
Yes. He told us all about you, Ana.
他觉得能够改变你有多值得
How he thought you were worthy, that he could change you.
但他错了
But he was wrong.
他为此而送了命
And it cost him his life.
他要杀我
He was gonna kill me.
他吗
Was he?
说够了没
Are you done?
是的  Ana  说完了
Yes, Ana. I'm done.
我这就完结了  对吗
So, this is it, huh?
是的  Henry
Yes, Henry.
了结了
This is it.
请听我说  好吗
I want you to listen to me, okay
因为我要你帮我个忙
because I will ask you a favor
我还没来得及换上参加父亲葬礼的衣服 就出现在你面前了
Chrissy, I'm standing in front of you in the same suit that I'm wearing to my father's funeral
我想请你帮个忙
and I'm asking you a favor.
我要在16小时内赶到洛杉矶
In 16 hours I need to land at LAX.
我还要棺材通过海关安检
I need that coffin to clear Customs
因为有灵车在那等着
because there will be a hearse waiting.
我要那灵车带着我和棺材
And I need that hearse to take me and that coffin
去墓地下葬  为什么
to a cemetery. Why,
chrissy  为什么不能让我带他回家入土
Chrissy? Why can't I just bring him to a funeral home
并安排所有的相关事宜
and make all the arrangements?
为什么我就不能在时限内搞定
Why can't I really take my time with it?
因为... 因为我要安顿好一切
Because...Because I need it to be done.
我要个终结
I need it to be over.
我只不过...
I just...
我只想安葬我父亲
I need to bury my father
有架飞机
That was an airplane.
不  我不在工作  我在悉尼
No, I'm not at work. I'm in Sydney.
对  澳大利亚
That's right. Australia.
我...
I...
我不知道  我...
I don't know, I...
我犯了个错误  妈妈
I made a mistake, Mom.
你知道的  所以我只能尽快远离你
You knew, so I got as far away from you as I could.
但是现在...
But now...
我想回家  妈妈
I wanna come home, Mommy.
那就回来吧
So come home.
我乘大洋航空
I'm on Oceanic Flight
815航班
815.
我会来接你的
I'll be there when you land, mija.
人都去哪了
Where is everybody?
你的话让他们忙活开了
What you said got them worked up.
他们去找Sawyer要回所有的枪
They went to get all the guns back from Sawyer.
Sawyer
所有的枪都在Sawyer那
Sawyer has all the guns?
说来话长
Long story.
至少你这支他就没有
At least he didn't get that one.
对的
Yeah.
但糟糕的是  我不能用它
Too bad I can't use it.
用来干什么
Use it on what?
我们抓住了一个人
We caught one of them.
他们中的一个人
The Others.
他被关在那里
He's locked up in there.
有多久了...
How long has he...
一个多星期
Over a week.
你负责守护他
And you're, what, taking care of him?
今天他想杀我
He tried to kill me today.
所以我要他死
So I wanted him dead.
但我做不到
I couldn't do it.
我就是下不了手
I couldn't even kill him.
我看着他
I looked at him, and he...
我怎么也做不到
I can't do this anymore.
那么让我来吧
Then let me do it.
他们都是禽兽
They're animals.
我亲眼看到他们的所作所为  他们真是禽兽不如
I've seen these people and they are animals.
他们从我手上抢走了我的儿子
They took my son. Right out of my hands.
他们抢走了我的儿子  还...
They took my son, and...
给我枪  我来
I'll do it. Give me the gun.
我杀了他
I'll kill him.
因为他们就是这么做的
'Cause that's what they'd do.
密码是多少
What's the combination?
右转18...
18 right.
左转1...
1 left.
右转31
31 right.
对不起
I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
Michael
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====